item_code	item_descr	item_order
A	A.    Facilitation of the intergovernmental process and expert bodies	1000
A1	"Parliamentary    documentation (number of documents, per entity/theme)"	1010
A2	"Substantive services for meetings (number of three-hour meetings, per entity/theme)"	1020
B	B.    Generation and transfer of knowledge	2000
B1	Field and technical cooperation projects (number of projects)	2010
B2	"Seminars, workshops and training events (number of days)"	2020
B3	Publications (number of publications)	2030
B4	Technical materials (number of materials)	2040
B5	"Fact-finding, monitoring and investigation missions (number of countries)"	2050
B6	Humanitarian assistance missions (number of countries)	2060
B7	Electoral missions (number of countries)	2070
C	C.    Substantive Deliverables	3000
C1	Good Offices	3010
C2	"Consultation, advice and advocacy"	3020
C3	Databases and substantive digital materials	3030
D	D.    Communication deliverables	4000
D1	"Outreach programmes, special events and information materials"	4010
D2	External and media relations	4020
D3	Digital platforms and multimedia content	4030
D4	Library services	4040
O	O.    OTHER	8000
OA1	Contribution to parliamentary documentation	8010
OA2	Contribution to substantive services for meetings	8020
OB2	"Contribution to a seminar, workshop or training event"	8030
OB3	Contribution to a publication	8040
OB4	Contribution to a technical material	8050
OC2	"Contribution to consultation, advice or advocacy deliverable"	8060
OC3	Contribution to a database or substantive digital material	8070
OD1	"Contribution to outreach programme, special event or information material"	8080
OD2	Contribution to external and media relations deliverable	8090
OD3	Contribution to a digital platform or multimedia content	8100
OE1	Evaluation	8200
